https://www.avantium.com/privacy-and-cookie-statement/

Privacy and cookie statementAvantium respects your privacy and complies with the provisions of the General Data Protection Regulation (‘GDPR’) and the Dutch Implementation Act and is committed to protecting your privacy on this website. For the purpose of this policy, Avantium refers to Avantium N.V., Zekeringstraat 29, 1014 BV Amsterdam, the Netherlands. Where personal data is processed by a subsidiary of Avantium N.V., this privacy statement applies in the same way.Purpose and lawfulness Your personal information, such as name, (email) addresses, telephone number and the like, is used by Avantium personnel, only for the purpose stated at the time it is collected. It is accessed by Avantium employees only on a need-to-know basis. Your personal data is never used for secondary or unrelated purposes unless otherwise requested or explicitly agreed by you. Purposes of data processing are to contact you or to keep you informed about Avantium, to reply to your questions, sending you press releases and other publications on the website and responding to your career application on the career site.When you apply for a job through our career page, you are requested to provide personal information related to the job application procedure, including in many instances a copy of your résumé. Your personal information is received directly by members of our human resources department, and is shared only with relevant Avantium staff members on a need-to-know basis. If the application process will not be continued with you, your personal data will be deleted after four (4) weeks after the closing of the procedure. In case you would like Avantium to keep your application and personal data in our talent pool, you can provide us your explicit consent for keeping your personal data for one (1) year.In any case, the legal basis of the mentioned processing is your explicit consent. If you have provided your consent for a particular processing, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. A withdrawal of your consent does not make previous processing – based on your permission – unlawful, but ensures that the processing must be terminated and your data (after the expiry of any storage period) must be destroyed.Third parties It is Avantium’s policy never to share, trade, sell or otherwise disclose personal information to third parties without your informed consent or direction, with the exceptions as mentioned in below.Personal data may be provided and processed by third parties – so called data processors – if this is necessary for the purpose of the processing. Avantium will arrange for data processing agreements with these data processors to secure your personal data.We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our rights (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.As a convenience to our visitors, www.avantium.com contains links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information (such as Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn, Facebook, and YouTube). Avantium is not responsible or liable for the content of those websites and the use of your personal data by those websites. This privacy and cookie statement does not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their data collection and distribution policies.Cookies Cookies are small text files that the website stores locally on your computer. Cookies allow Avantium for example to recognize your computer the next time you visit us. By doing so, we are able to improve user-friendliness of the website and to adjust the website to your needs.Avantium shall only store so called “cookies” on your computer when you have provided us with your consent by clicking on the appropriate button during your visit of our website.You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse receiving it. You can also withdraw your consent at all times by re-entering our website and select the right options. By changing settings, you can also determine that your browser will not accept cookies from this website. Be aware that in such events you may no longer be able to use all the possibilities and features of our website.Cookies used Avantium collects information that you voluntarily submit to us, e.g. by completing forms on our website, by registering for a conference or by participating in an online survey.Avantium uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, to help the website analyze how users use the site. Avantium will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. These cookies are automatically deleted after 6 months.Your rights When requested, we grant visitors access to all their personal information we have collected. When requested, we offer visitors the possibility of correcting any incorrect personal information we may have collected or remove any personal information we may have collected. If you wish access to your information, or correcting or removal of your personal data, please contact us at the address or contact information in below.Furthermore, based on the GDPR you have a right to submit a complaint to the Dutch Data Protection Authority against our processing of your personal data. You can contact the Dutch Data Protection Authority for this directly.Contact / questions? If you wish to contact us with regards to this statement or the processing of your personal data via our webiste, you can reach us in the following ways:Avantium N.V. Via email: info@avantium.com By telephone: +31-20-586 8080 By mail: Zekeringstraat 29, 1014 BV Amsterdam, The NetherlandsAvantium has the right to amend this privacy and cookie statement if needed or desired.
×
Trudy SchoolenbergTrudy Schoolenberg joined the Supervisory Board of the Company in September 2020.Dr. Trudy Schoolenberg served in various senior management positions at Shell, Wärtsilä and Akzo-Nobel in Research, Operations and Strategy. Dr. Schoolenberg currently holds Senior Independent Director roles at Spirax Sarco Engineering Plc, and Accsys Technologies Plc. Additionally, she is a Non-Eexecutive Director (Bestuurslid) of The Netherlands Petroleum Stockpiling Agency (COVA). Dr. Schoolenberg has a Ph.D. in Technical Sciences at the Delft University of Technology (The Netherlands) and an Msc in Industrial Engineering.  She certified as a Non Execitive Director at ESAA, Erasmus University Rotterdam.
×
Cynthia ArnoldCynthia Arnold joined the Supervisory Board of the Company in September 2020.She served as Senior Vice President and Chief Technology Officer at The Valspar Corporation, a manufacturer of paint and coatings. She was also Chief Technology Officer at Sun Chemical Corporation, the world’s largest producer of printing inks and pigments. Prior to this, she worked for nine years at General Electric Plastics, of which three years were for GE Plastics Europe in The Netherlands. She currently serves as a non-executive Director on the Boards of The Cabot Corporation, Milliken & Company and Citrine Informatics.Dr. Cynthia Arnold holds a Ph.D. from the Virginia Polytechnic Institute & State University in Blacksburg (USA), an MBA from the University of California in Berkeley (USA) and a BS in Chemical Engineering from the University of California in Berkely (USA).
×Extraordinary General Meeting of Shareholders 2020More detailed information about the extraordinary general meeting of shareholders (30 September 2020) can be found here:CEO Invitation to EGM 2020 >Convocation notice >Agenda and explanatory notes EGM Avantium N.V. 30 September 2020 >Annex I Power of attorney >Voting results >Introduction Cynthia Arnold >Introduction Trudy Schoolenberg >Questions shareholders >
×
Michelle JouMichelle Jou joined the Supervisory Board of the Company in 2020. She has over 20 years of professional experience in the chemical industry in Asia and Europe, where she has served in a variety of positions in sales, marketing and supply chain management. In 2003, Michelle Jou joined Covestro (formerly Bayer MaterialScience) in the company’s central departments in Shanghai. She later took on the role of VP of the Polycarbonates Business Unit in China and Hong Kong. In 2012 Mrs. Jou was named Senior VP of Commercial Operations in the Asia region. In 2016, she became President of Covestro’s global Polycarbonates Segment, headquartered in Shanghai.Mrs. Michelle B.B. Jou (1969) holds a Bachelor of Arts degree in French from Fu-Jen University (Taiwan) and an MBA from the EMLYON Business School (France). She is fluent in Mandarin, Cantonese, French and English.
×
×
Bart WeltenChief Financial OfficerMr Welten will bring 30 years in finance to Avantium and has extensive experience in the chemical and life-sciences industries. He most recently served as the CFO of Centrient Pharmaceuticals (formerly the joint-venture of DSM and Sinochem) in Singapore. Before he left Centrient, he managed the sale of the company to Bain Capital.  Prior to this, Mr Welten held the position of CFO of DSM Resins and DSM Anti-Infectives. He holds a law degree from Leiden University (Netherlands) and an MBA from Boston College (USA).
×
Edwin MosesChairEdwin Moses (chairman) joined the Supervisory Board of the Company in December 2019.Edwin Moses is a serial entrepreneur and value creator in European life science companies. He has expertise in high value service provision to the pharmaceutical industry and in drug discovery and development. His primary focus is on high growth businesses and change management. Mr. Moses has 25 years of Board level experience in more than 10 companies, mostly as Chairman.Edwin Moses is Chairman of the Supervisory Board and member of the Audit Committee.
×crisis test
Resources
×
×
×
×
×
×
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse and use the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.OkPrivacy policy
